You can't break up with your past.
Love Hurts is a action, comedy, romance film directed by Jonathan Eusebio.
A realtor is pulled back into the life he left behind after his former
partner-in-crime resurfaces with an ominous message.
With his crime-lord brother also on his trail, he must confront
his past and the history he never fully buried.
Marvin Gable, played by Ke Huy Quan.
Rose Carlisle, played by Ariana DeBose.
Alvin 'Knuckles' Gable, played by Daniel Wu.
The Raven, played by Mustafa Shakir.
Ashley, played by Lio Tipton.
Renny Merlo, played by Cam Gigandet.
Love Hurts is a 2025 American action comedy film directed by Jonathan Eusebio, in his
directorial debut, and written by Matthew Murray, Josh Stoddard, and Luke Passmore.
The film stars Ke Huy Quan, Ariana DeBose, Daniel Wu, Mustafa Shakir,
Lio Tipton, Cam Gigandet, Marshawn Lynch, and Sean Astin.
Its plot follows a former hitman-turned-realtor who learns that his brother
is hunting him when he reunites with his former partner.
The film was released in the United States on
February 7, 2025, by Universal Pictures.
It received generally negative reviews from critics and earned $17.6 million
worldwide on the budget of $18 million becoming a box office bomb.
The film explores themes of martial arts, sibling
relationship, hitman, strip club, real estate agent.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.